fee.org 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - Foundation for Economic Education

This privacy policy sets out how the Foundation for Economic Education (FEE) uses and protects any information that you give FEE when you use this website and FEE's mobile applications.

FEE is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website and mobile applications, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

FEE may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from March 30, 2016. Updated: May 17, 2018.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * name
  * contact information including email address and phone number
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences, and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails and SMS messages about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
  * FEE may share any content I submit to FEE with other organizations and individuals so that I can be made aware of opportunities that FEE thinks may be of interest to me and to otherwise advance FEE’s educational mission.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Third-Party Privacy Policies

FEE utilizes a number of third-party softwares and services that may handle some personal information. These services' policies can be found here:

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Children

Our products and services are generally not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 without parental consent. If you become aware that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without parental consent, please let us know so we can take appropriate action.

## Controlling your personal information

If you have previously agreed to allow your personal information to be used for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b8cfdddad5d9cbccddcaf8fefdfd96d7cadf).

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#087f6d6a65697b7c6d7a484e4d4d26677a6f). We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

If you receive an SMS message and would like to stop all further SMS communication, reply to the message with "STOP".

Disable push notifications [here](https://fee.org/my-account/notifications/).

## Donor Privacy Policy

The Foundation for Economic Education respects the privacy of its donors and their choice not to have personal information shared. FEE does not sell, rent, or trade donor information (collected online or offline) to organizations that use such information for commercial purposes. Occasionally, FEE makes donor lists available for limited, one-time use by selected nonprofits in return for donor lists from those organizations. This helps FEE continue to grow its global base of support.

FEE donors may request that their contact information be excluded from any list exchanges. Please direct all such requests to Aaron Brown by emailing [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), calling (404) 554-9980, or writing to FEE, 1819 Peachtree Road NE, Suite 300, Atlanta, GA 30309. We will honor such requests immediately.
